{
    "subject": "King_Vidor",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Wild_Oranges",
    "human_readable": "King Vidor created Wild Oranges.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7383453845977783,
            "question": "Did King Vidor direct any other films besides Wild Oranges?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7231121063232422,
            "question": "Who created the film Wild Oranges?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6901506781578064,
            "question": "When was Wild Oranges created?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6188347935676575,
            "question": "What was King Vidor known for creating?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.530899703502655,
            "question": "What type of work did King Vidor create?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3540220558643341,
            "question": "Is Wild Oranges a movie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3470849096775055,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the film Wild Oranges?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.325624018907547,
            "question": "What genre is the film Wild Oranges?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21195454895496368,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by King Vidor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18748120963573456,
            "question": "Name a film directed by King Vidor."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=King Vidor created Wild Oranges.",
            "html": "yago_21668_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the film directed by King Vidor?",
            "html": "yago_21668_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Wild Oranges?",
            "html": "yago_21668_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about the film Wild Oranges?",
            "html": "yago_21668_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21668_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21668_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21668_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21668_128.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21668_137.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21668_154.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21668_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21668_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21668_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21668_58.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\n**Explanation:** The context information provides details about a film titled \"Wild Oranges,\" directed by King Vidor and based on a story by Joseph Hergesheimer. Additionally, there is an excerpt from the Project Gutenberg EBook of \"Wild Oranges\" by Joseph Hergesheimer, indicating that it was produced as a movie with King Vidor as one of the creators (both as director and writer). Therefore, the triple \"King Vidor created Wild Oranges\" is supported by the documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}